ringnrock.com 2011-09-20

# Ringtone downloads | Ringtones for ATT, T-Mobile, Verizon and more | RingNRock.com

#### Last updated December 07, 2009

This Privacy Policy for www.RingNRock.com outlines important information regarding the use and disclosure of information collected via this Website (defined below). RingNRock provides this Privacy Policy to help users make an informed decision as to whether to use or continue using the Website. If you have any questions about the RingNRock Service, please see our full [FAQ](http://www.ringnrock.com/help/index.php?page=faqs), or contact our Customer Care team at [Contact Us](http://www.ringnrock.com/index.php?page=contactus).  If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement on the home page and on any other place we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently.  If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you as described above.

IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY PLEASE DO NOT PROVIDE ANY INFORMATION TO RINGNROCK OR USE ANY OF THE SERVICES OR PRODUCTS OFFERED OR PROVIDED ON ANY OF THE WEBSITES REFERRED TO IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY. 

This Privacy Policy applies to RingNRock's collection, use, storage and disclosure of information by RingNRock on its websites, (collectively, the "Website"), and to RingNRock's other information collection, including the purchase of customer lists from third parties. RingNRock is not responsible for the information collection or privacy practices of third party web sites or applications. By reference, this Privacy Policy is incorporated into and is subject to the Website [Terms and Conditions](http://www.ringnrock.com/help/index.php?page=terms). Your use of the Website and any personal information you provide via the Website or through other official RingNRock contact remains subject to this Privacy Policy, as well as the Terms and Conditions and/or other stated policies.

## Part 1\. Information Collection

## 1.0 General Data Collection. 

## Registration 

In order to use the services on the Website, you must provide your cell phone number. We use this information to contact you about the services on our site in which you have expressed interest.  After you enter your cell phone number and sign up for a service, we will share your cell phone number with necessary third parties such as wireless carriers and third party business partners who verify, for example, your carrier and your ability to incur charges on your cell phone plan. You have the option to provide demographic information (such as income level and gender) to us in the “my library” section of the Website; we encourage you to submit this information so we can provide you a more personalized experience on our site. You can also update your information in “my library” by logging in to your account and updating your information.  

#### 1.1 Survey Information.

RingNRock collects information from individuals by various methods, including, but not limited to, when an individual voluntarily completes a RingNRock survey, order form, or a registration page either online, or by means of online or offline surveys, order forms, or registration pages operated by third parties (collectively, a "Survey"). As used herein, "online" means using the Internet, including the Website, and related technologies. In the Surveys, RingNRock or a third party (a "Third Party") may ask an individual to provide various information to RingNRock, which may include his or her name, email address, street address, zip code, telephone number(s) (including cell phone number(s) and carrier(s)), SMS messaging details (e.g. date, time and content of the SMS message), birth date, gender, salary range, education and marital status, occupation, employment information, personal and online interests, and such other information as may be requested from time to time (together, "Survey Information"). RingNRock may also collect information concerning an individual from another source and use that information in combination with information provided from this Website. Completing the Surveys is completely voluntary, and individuals are under no obligation to provide Survey Information to RingNRock or a Third Party, but an individual may receive incentives from RingNRock or a Third Party in exchange for providing Survey Information to RingNRock. 

#### 1.2 Third Party List Information.

RingNRock collects information from individuals when an individual provides information to a Third Party and RingNRock subsequently purchases, licenses, or otherwise acquires the information from the Third Party (the "Seller"). Such purchased information may include, but is not limited to, an individual's name, email address, street address, zip code, telephone numbers (including cell phone numbers and carriers), SMS messaging details (e.g. date, time and content of the SMS message), birth date, gender, salary range, education and marital status, occupation, industry of employment, personal and online interests, and such other information as the individual may have provided to the Seller (together, "Third Party List Information"). When acquiring Third Party List Information, RingNRock seeks assurances from the Seller that the Seller has a right to transfer the Third Party List Information to RingNRock and that the Seller has a right to provide offers from advertisers to the individuals whose personal information is included on the Seller's list.

#### 1.3 Other Information.

Other occasions when RingNRock obtains information from individuals include but are not limited to (1) when an individual is making a claim for a prize or seeking to redeem an incentive offered by RingNRock or by a Third Party, (2) when an individual requests assistance through RingNRock's customer service department, and/or (3) when an individual voluntarily subscribes to a RingNRock service (together, "Other Information").

#### 1.4 Cookies, Web Beacons, and Other Info Collected Using Technology.

RingNRock currently uses cookie and web beacon technology to associate certain Internet-related information about an individual with information about the individual in our database. Additionally, RingNRock may use other new and evolving sources of information in the future (together, "Technology Information").

(a) Cookies. A cookie is a small amount of data stored on the hard drive of the individual's computer that allows RingNRock to identify the individual with his or her corresponding data that resides in RingNRock's database. You may read more about cookies at [cookiecentral.com](http://cookiecentral.com/) and elsewhere on the Internet. Individuals who use the Website need to accept cookies in order to use all of the features and functionality of the Website. Our cookies are linked to your personal information during each individual user session. 

(b) Web Beacons. A web beacon is programming code that can be used to display an image on a web page, but can also be used to transfer an individual's unique user identification (often in the form of a cookie) to a database and associate the individual with previously acquired information about an individual in a database. This allows RingNRock to track certain web sites an individual visits online. Web beacons are used to determine products or services an individual may be interested in, and to track online behavioral habits for marketing purposes. For example, RingNRock might place, with the consent of a Third Party website, a web beacon on the Third Party's website where baseball products are sold. When Joe, an individual listed in RingNRock's database, visits the baseball website, RingNRock receives notice by means of the web beacon that Joe visited the baseball site, and RingNRock would then update Joe's profile with the information that Joe is interested in baseball. RingNRock may thereafter present offers of baseball related products and services to Joe. In addition to using web beacons on web pages, RingNRock also uses web beacons in email messages sent to individuals listed in RingNRock's database.

(c) New Technology. The use of technology on the Internet, including cookies and web beacons, is rapidly evolving, as is RingNRock's use of new and evolving technology. As a result, RingNRock strongly encourages individuals to revisit this policy for any updates regarding its use of technology.

#### 1.5 Outside Information.

RingNRock may receive and supplement information about individuals from Third Parties or from other sources of information outside of RingNRock including information located in public databases ("Outside Information").

#### 1.6 Personal Information.

As used herein, Personal Information means any information that can identify an individual, such as name, phone number, email and address. This may be collected by us through Survey Information, Third Party List Information, Other Information, Technology Information, and Outside Information, and any other information RingNRock gathers or receives about individuals such as usage data, file transfer data and viewing data.

#### 1.7 No Information Collected from Children.

RingNRock will never knowingly collect any personal information about children under the age of thirteen (13). If RingNRock obtains actual knowledge that it has collected personal information about a child under the age of thirteen (13), that information will be maintained solely for regulatory compliance purposes. RingNRock has designed this policy in order to comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act ("COPPA").

#### 1.8 Log File Information.

When users log in to access their account, our servers may automatically record and archive certain information that web-browsers send whenever visiting a Website. These server logs may include information vital to validating the user's authorization to access the account. Information, such as a web request, Internet Protocol (the "IP") address, browser type, browser language, referring pages, exit pages and visited URLs, platform type, click counts, pages viewed and in what order, time spent, the date and time of the request, and other important data is necessary to validate and authorize a user's entry and activity on the Website.

## Part 2\. Personal Information Usage

#### 2.1 Discretion to Use Information.

RINGNROCK MAY USE YOUR INFORMATION FOR ANY LEGALLY PERMISSIBLE PURPOSE IN COMPANY'S SOLE DISCRETION. The following paragraphs in Section 2 describe how RingNRock currently uses Personal Information, but RingNRock may change or broaden its use at any time. As noted, RingNRock may update this policy from time to time.  RingNRock on its own behalf or by using one of its service providers may use Personal Information to provide promotional offers to individuals by means of email advertising, telephone marketing, direct mail marketing, and package stuffers, among other possible uses. If we perform any of these functions, we will give you the option to opt out of receiving this information. 

#### 2.2 Solicited Email and SMS Messages.

RingNRock only sends SMS messages and customer service emails to individuals who have agreed on the Website to receive SMS messages and email from RingNRock during service initiation and activation and as a part of the Services. RingNRock does not send unsolicited SMS or email messages.  As a result, statutes requiring certain formatting for unsolicited email are not applicable to RingNRock's email messages.

#### 2.3 Targeted Advertising.

RingNRock on its own behalf or by using one of its service providers may use Personal Information to target advertising to an individual.  When an individual is using the Internet, RingNRock uses Technology Information (see also Section 2.5 below) to associate an individual with that person's Personal Information, and RingNRock attempts to show advertising for products and services in which the person has expressed an interest in the Surveys, indicated an interest by means of Technology Information, and otherwise. RingNRock may, at its discretion, target advertising by using email, direct mail, telephones, cell phones, and other means of communication to provide promotional offers.  You can opt out of receiving this advertising by emailing us at the email below. 

#### 2.4 Mobile Phone SMS Messaging.

In certain cases, when requested by an individual, RingNRock or a Third Party may use Personal Information to provide customized content and advertising via SMS messaging to an individual's cell phone. RingNRock is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Third Parties.

#### 2.5 Use of Technology Information.

RingNRock uses Technology Information (1) to match a person's Survey Information and Third Party List Information to other categories of Personal Information to make and improve profiles of individuals, (2) to track a person's online browsing habits on the Internet, and (3) to determine which areas of RingNRock's websites are most frequently visited. This information helps RingNRock to better understand the online habits of individuals so that RingNRock can target advertising and promotions to them. 

#### 2.6 Profiles of Individuals.

RingNRock supplements Personal Information to make a profile of an individual. A profile can be created by combining Survey Information and Third Party List Information with other sources of Personal Information such as information obtained from public databases.

#### 2.7 Storage of Personal Information.

RingNRock stores the Personal Information in a database on RingNRock computers. Our computers have security measures (such as a firewall and access control list) in place to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under RingNRock's control. Notwithstanding such measures, RingNRock cannot guarantee that its security measures will prevent RingNRock computers from being illegally accessed, and the Personal Information on them stolen or altered. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure.  Therefore, while we strive to protect your personal information, we do not and cannot guarantee its security. 

## Part 3\. Personal Information Dissemination

#### 3.1 Third Parties.

RingNRock operates sites on behalf of some of its customers (for example, other businesses that contract with us to operate mobile storefronts or other services for them). When we operate sites on behalf of such customers, we may disclose your information (including personally identifiable information) to them when you provide it to us as part of registering for those sites or "opting in" for promotions, programs or offerings from those customers. Our customers will use and disclose the information we provide them pursuant to their own policies regarding such information. RingNRock also maintains channels and other features on RingNRock's own site(s) in cooperation with third parties (e.g., to feature the work of certain musicians or other artists, or record labels/publishers), and we may disclose your email address, telephone number or mobile identification number, and other personally identifiable information to such third parties when you provide it to us as part of subscribing to such channels or features. RingNRock's customers and other third parties that we cooperate with will use and disclose the information we provide them pursuant to their own policies regarding such information. We recommend that you review those policies before providing us with personal information in connection with sites, promotions, programs or offerings from such customers and third parties, and before subscribing to channels or features we operate in cooperation with customers or third parties. In addition, traffic data and personal data may be used by RingNRock for editorial and feedback purposes, for marketing and promotional purposes, for statistical analysis of users' behavior, for product development, for site improvement, and to inform advertisers of how many visitors have seen or clicked on their advertisements or viewed their promotions. In these cases, data is maintained and reviewed on an aggregate (i.e., group) basis. We may share this information with our customers and other parties, but when we do so it does not include personally identifying information. In addition, we use traffic and personal data to customize and tailor your experience on RingNRock sites, such as to help us display content that we think you may be interested in.

**Service Providers**

We use other third parties such as a live chat and customer service provider to provide services on our site.  When you use these services, we will share your information as necessary for the third party to provide that service.  These third parties use your personally indefinable information to fulfill the necessary service.

**Information Sharing**

RingNRock does not share Personal Information with third parties for promotional or marketing purposes unrelated to our mobile services without your consent nor do we sell your personal information to third parties.  

#### 3.2 Legal Process.

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site.

#### 3.3 Summary Data.

RingNRock may sell or transfer non-individualized information, such as summary or aggregated anonymous information about all persons or sub-groups of persons.

##  

## Part 4\. Privacy Practices of Third Parties

#### 4.1 Advertiser cookies and web beacons.

Advertising agencies, advertising networks, and other companies (together, "Advertisers") who place advertisements on the Website and on the Internet generally may use their own cookies, web beacons, and other technology to collect information about individuals. RingNRock does not control Advertisers' use of such technology and RingNRock has no responsibility for the use of such technology to gather information about individuals.

#### 4.2 Links.

The Website and email messages sometimes contain hypertext links to the websites of Third Parties. RingNRock is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other websites. Linked websites may contain links to websites maintained by Third Parties. Such links are provided for your convenience and reference only. RingNRock does not operate or control in any respect any information, software, products or services available on such Third Party websites. The inclusion of a link to a website does not imply any endorsement of the services or the site, its contents, or its sponsoring organization. We strongly advise you to read the privacy policies of these Third Parties. 

#### 4.3 Affiliated Companies.

Should RingNRock be subject to an acquisition, merger, sale or other change of control or business entity status, RingNRock reserves the right to transfer or assign the Information collected from the Website to a successor entity. In the event of such a transfer or assignment, the successor entity shall be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. Please see above to see how you will be notified. 

##  

## Part 5\. Individuals Outside of the United States

Currently the Website is only for United States citizens or persons legally residing in the United States or its territories. Anyone using the Website outside of the United States acknowledges that personal information will be collected and stored by RingNRock in the United States. By using the Website, you consent to the transfer of information to and/or storage of information outside of your country and in the United States.

##  

## Part 6\. Cancellation Procedures

If you wish to discontinue receiving messages from RingNRock, you must cancel your subscription. You have several options to do this:

#### 6.1 Cancel via an SMS message.

To cancel your subscription via an SMS message, text "STOP", "END", or "QUIT" to 72825.

#### 6.2 Cancel via the Website.

To cancel your subscription via the Website, please see [Customer Care](http://www.ringnrock.com/index.php?action=unsubscribe). 

**6.3 Questions.**

MBmobile, LLC, the owner and operator of the Website, is a licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy Program.  TRUSTe is an independent, organization whose mission is to build user’s trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices.  This privacy statement covers the website www.RingNRock.com.  Because this Website wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact [legaladministrator@mbmobile.com](mailto:legaladministrator@mbmobile.com) or MBmobile, LLC, 1490 W. 121st Ave. Ste 210, Westminster, CO 80234, Attn:  Legal Administrator.  If you do not receive acknowledgement of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should contact TRUSTe at [http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint&url](http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint&url). TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with us to resolve your concerns. 

**If you have questions about this policy, please contact us at**[ legalnotices@mbmobile.com](mailto:legalnotices@mbmobile.com) **.**  
**  
California User Consumer Rights.**   In accordance with California Civil Code Sec. 1789.3, California resident users are entitled to know that they may file grievances and complaints with California Department of Consumer Affairs, 400 R Street, STE 1080, Sacramento, CA 95814; or by phone at 916-445-1254 or 800-952-5210; or by email to dca@dca.ca.gov.
